lemmecheck.com 2004-06-05

# LemmeCheck Entertainment : Glamour Models, Supermodels and Entertainment

|  |   
---  
  
| 

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**GENERAL OVERVIEW**

LemmeCheck Entertainment Group is dedicated to honoring the privacy of every visitor to our sites, whether you are linking to us, searching for information on our site, or just passing through. The Staff at LemmeCheck will not gather information from you for the purposes of distributing **any** personally identifiable information to third parties. This statement of our privacy policy is offered to provide you with a working knowledge of the manner in which this site operates so you can lay your privacy concerns to rest and to inform you of the information we do collect and the purpose of that information. We present that information to you in an easy to use format. Please view the information contained on this page first. If your issue is not adequately addressed, please contact the legal department. You will receive a response within seven (7) days.

This site contains links to other sites. LemmeCheck.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We thank you for your patronage. Do not hesitate to contact us with any and all questions and concerns.

 _\--The LemmeCheck Staff_

* * *

**SPECIFIC STATEMENTS**

  1. **What information does LemmeCheck gather and for what purpose?**  
We gather different information from different visitors, depending upon your level of interaction with our site:
    1. **General Users**.   Our search-capable scripts automatically gather certain information from you, regarding only the latest version of the page you are viewing, so that it may timely update the page with new submissions. No personally identifiable information is collected or disseminated in any way simply by you accessing our search engine services.
    2. **Opt-In Email/Newsletter Updates.**    By signing up for e-mail updates, we request your name and valid e-mail address. We will not ever willfully sell or otherwise distribute this information to any third party without first obtaining your permission. The purpose of this information is to send you the requested update information regarding changes to our site. We may, from time to time, send you brief e-mails for the purpose of quality control and/or to determine if we are meeting our responsibility to you regarding your experiences on our sites, as well as to provide you with updates about our website. You may unsubscribe from this list automatically, as every e-mail so instructs.
    3. **Linked Content.**    For our visitors who link their sites to our search engine, or HotList, we require information to ensure accuracy and validity of the link. We offer you the ability to edit your link at any time. While we may, from time to time, send you mail in order to ensure proper listing, or to update your link, we will not distribute any of your information, other than that made available to the public at your request. Access your search engine account via the "Modify Your Site form". If you are unable, for any reason, to access your account, simply send an e-mail to the webmaster and state the problem you are experiencing modifying the link from the site.
    4. **Featured Models, Sites, Cover Models, Contestants, Other Submissions.**    We offer a variety of features based on information through requests from various models, photographers, artists and other industry professionals. Information requested includes your name, a static e-mail address, if applicable, personal statistics, web site url and other information that you give us for the purpose of entering our contest or reviewing your site or otherwise featuring your submitted information. This information will be published if accepted per your permission. If the submission is in error in any way, you may e-mail the Editor at any time.
    5. **Advertisers**
      1. _Banner Exchange Clients_.   We request information from our Banner Exchange Clients, including name and email address, in order to ensure that they may be promptly alerted when a banner is broken, and to ensure the validity of the account. We may, from time to time, send email for quality control purposes or to ensure that we are fulfilling our responsibility to our Banner Exchange Clients in providing a high quality service.
      2. _Other Advertisers and Sponsors_.   We require information from our advertisers and sponsors, including name, company name, billing address, email address and telephone number, so that we may properly set up and maintain their accounts, to ensure prompt response in the event of a broken link or banner, and to ensure validity of the account. We may, from time to time, send mail for quality control purposes or to ensure that we are fulfilling our responsibilities to the advertiser or sponsor with regard to the services offered.
    6. **Cookies**
      1. _Advertisers_.   We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we _do not_ have access to this information.
      2. _In-House Advertisements_.   We rent ad space for various locations on our site and use a banner rotation software to rotate the various advertisements. This software will set a cookie to prevent caching of advertisements thereby allowing for the rotation of various advertising creatives.
  2. **What about aggregate or demographic information?**  
In order to provide relevant content of interest to you, our visitor, we may collect demographic information which may be shared with our advertisers or sponsors, or internally. This will be for the main purpose of providing you with a more satisfactory service, tailored to your interests and needs. All information would be shared as an aggregate, with no personally identifiable information exchanged without your permission.
  3. **Public Forums**  
This site occasionally makes forums and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
  4. **Security**  
LemmeCheck has in place several security features to protect your submitted information. The only information contained online is that which is submitted as part of your search engine listing, forum profile, and hotlist information. All data submitted here is contained with a password protected area of the web server and, for the most part, is encrypted and/or is contained within an area not viewable by web browsers except for purposes of editing by the owner of the submitted data.

In addition, an authentication process is in place to ensure only owners of submitted data may access their information, or edit any information contained within.

Further, we utilize tailor-made software whose primany function is detection and blocking of hacking attempts and brute force password guessing software. Users engaging in this type of activity are detected and reported to their respective ISP's and, where applicable, law enforcement agencies.

  5. **What if I enter personal information by mistake?**  
Please refer to section 1. above for information regarding editing your account or modifying your link. Should you have additional questions regarding our privacy policy, please address them to the webmaster.

We hope you enjoy your visit with LemmeCheck Entertainment.  
  
---  
  
|   
«« Submit Listing |  Edit Listing  |  Advertisers  |  [](http://www.lemmecheck.com/wodbabes/nude.jpg)Helpdesk  |  About Us  |  Copyright  |  Disclaimer  |  Privacy Statement  |  Contact Us »»
